# **Curriculum Vitae**

ST#7 PHEROZ PARK 2 LAHORE, GREEN TOWN +92 312 4874118 shampytechnical@gmail.com

# Shahzaib Ali Tariq



#### **SKILLS**

I have been working as a graphics designer as a freelancer and Joined DK Recruitment as an Intern for about 4 - 5 months. I started web development after college. Now I have skills with Node Js, Express, HTML, CSS & JavaScript. Being a Full Stack Web Developer. I learned web designing with Figma and Illustrator.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **DK Recruitment, Gulberg 3** — Intern

JANUARY 2022 - MAY 2022

- Social Media Marketing, Advertisements
- Web Development
- Graphics Designing

#### **NooreAzal Foundation, Freelancer** — Content Management

**SEPTEMBER 2021 - JULY 2022** 

- Content Management
- Data Management
- Web Designing

# **EDUCATION**

# Junior Officers High School, PCSIR 2 — Matric

JANUARY 2018 - MARCH 2020, PCSIR 2

## **Government College, Township** — *Inter*

SEPTEMBER 2021 - AUGUST 2022, Township Near Dolphin HeadQuarters.

#### **AWARDS**

Website Completion By DK Recruitment.

Article Writing & Content Management By NooreAzal Foundation